{
    "subject": "resource/Vodohod",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Vodohod",
    "human_readable": "The name of Vodohod is Vodohod.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789205193519592,
            "question": "Is the name of Vodohod, Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9603655934333801,
            "question": "What is the name of Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9405257105827332,
            "question": "What is referred to as Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392498135566711,
            "question": "Give me the name that belongs to Vodohod."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9102693200111389,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name associated with Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8611176609992981,
            "question": "If someone asked for the name of Vodohod, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8546941876411438,
            "question": "What term represents Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7544147968292236,
            "question": "What's the identity of Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6652079224586487,
            "question": "How would you describe Vodohod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6080869436264038,
            "question": "What is the label given to Vodohod?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Vodohod is Vodohod.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4723_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Vodohod?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4723_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What's the identity of Vodohod?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4723_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What term represents Vodohod?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4723_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4723_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the cruise operator Vodohod, including its name and activities. Therefore, the statement \"The name of Vodohod is Vodohod\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}